We are now joined by the 37th pick
overall in the 2026 draft, the newest
member of the New York Giants from the
University of Tennessee. Please welcome
Caden the Hood. Congratulations and
welcome to Giants family, Caden.
Yes, sir. Thank you. I'm glad to be
here.
Take me through the when you got the
phone call, what were the first kind of
kind of thing few few things that ran
through your mind as you realized that
you were a New York Giant?
Uh definitely definitely just, you know,
realization I'm going to be able to live
my dream.
Uh you know, I'm just I'm so happy and
ecstatic, you know what I'm saying, to
get to play for such a storied franchise
and
I'm just happy to be here. Happy to get
the opportunity and you know, and I'm
going to work my butt off so I can be
the best version of myself, so
All right, so obviously you you are a
fan of press coverage. You like that
man-to-man coverage. What is it about
that aspect of the coverage that you
like?
Uh just just like I said, the
competition part of it.
Just the one-on-ones, you know, on the
outside. I don't think it gets any more
competitive than that, you know, in the
sport. All right, great. So, listen, as
a corner, obviously everybody talks
about your coverage skills and, you
know, how you handle that from a press
coverage standpoint, but you also you
like to come up and and lay some licks
down there. You like to come up and
tackle.
What what what kind of what kind of How
would you describe your tackling
ability?
Uh yeah, I would just describe it as
somebody who
you know, who just loves the game, you
know what I'm saying? Tackling is a part
of the game,
you know, so I love the game, so that's
just, you know, something that is a part
of it and something I want to do.
And then it's also like I I said, I'm a
competitor, you know what I'm saying? If
that's part of the game, that's part of
competing. I can't call myself a
competitor if I don't want to tackle, so
Well, listen, Caden, congratulations on
becoming the newest member of the New
York Giants. We can't wait for you to
get here and and to compete and to put
on that blue jersey. Congratulations.
See you soon. Yes, sir. Appreciate you.
>> [music]